<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bug Bounty on Vishal Uniyal</title>
    <link>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/tags/bug-bounty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bug Bounty on Vishal Uniyal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/tags/bug-bounty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2 Deliverable: Reflection</title>
      <link>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/reflectionblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/reflectionblog/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Week 2 has been a very interesting week where I went deeper into cyber security knowledge base. It had been a great experience with the subject so far, I had been involved in fixing my website, working on challenges on PentesterLab, Juice-shop, Hackthebox.eu, writing and researching blogs such as hackerOne, BugsCrowd and working out the real life issues with the security in a company&amp;rsquo;s online network and the various ways it can be exploited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2 HomeWork 2 : Problem Statement on Web-application Security</title>
      <link>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/week2friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/week2friday/</guid>
      <description>OWASP XSS Introduction Web applications are susceptible to attacks that may result in exposure or modification of sensitive data, or impact on availability of services to authorized users. Application testing is conducted to identify security flaws introduced in the design, implementation or deployment of an application. Developers and application administrators must identify functions that are critical to security and test those functions to verify correct operation.
Problem Statement #1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Cross Site Scripting (XSS) is a fairly widespread input sanitization failure (essentially a special case of common mistake #1).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3 Reflection: Problem Statement on Web-application Security</title>
      <link>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/week3blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/week3blog/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2 : Ethical Hacking &amp; Bug Bounties</title>
      <link>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/week1blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/week1blog/</guid>
      <description>Ethical hacking and bug bounties are becomming popular these days, and they are getting paid well for this job. Professtional Ethical Hackers working for big organisations are responsible to test break into the company and systems and develop reports to fix these issue. Where as Bug Bounty hunters are individuals or group of people who find ways to break into company&amp;rsquo;s network and report it to the company they hacked, where they get paid as Bounty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 : SUMMER STUDIOS CYBER SECURITY: AN OFFENSIVE MINDSET</title>
      <link>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/week2blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://VishalUniyal.gitlab.io/blog/week2blog/</guid>
      <description>Experience I am a final year International Student of Bachelors of Engineering in ICT and Software Engineering at University of Technology Sydney (UTS). I am in a five-year Engineering Degree programme to include Diploma in Engineering Practice. As a student I am still finding my career &#34;End Goal&#34;, and I like familiarising myself with multiple disciplines of computer Software and Security.  I have experience of working for software companies as an Application/Website Developer and Quality Assurance - Internship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>